Bryan Dang

Software Developer

CONTACT

- 301-848-0407
- bdang160@gmail.com
- **Q** Elkridge, MD, USA
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryandang96/

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science

University of Maryland College Park, MD | 2018

SKILLS / TOOLS

- Secret Security Clearance
- Java
- **■** C, C++
- Qt Creator
- Visual Studio, Eclipse, Netbeans
- Docker
- Git, Clearcase
- Jira, Rally
- Documentation
- Debugging, Testing

INTERESTS

Chess, Guitar, Weightlifting, Board Games, Dungeons and Dragons

PROFILE

Reliable software developer with 3 years experience who is interested in fullstack development of high-level applications. Experienced in working with Object Oriented Programming Languages such as Java and C++. Strong team-player who is capable of communicating design ideas with team members and solving problems together.

EXPERIENCE

Northrop Grumman

Software Engineer | Linthicum, MD | July 2018 - PRESENT

- (Mission Systems) Designed a sensor API that users can interface with to ingest F-35 sensor data. | C++, Git, Docker, Visual Studio
- (Mission Systems) Built a reference implementation of the sensor API to show future developers how to use the API. | C++, Git, Docker, Visual Studio
- (Mission Security) Created a command-line version of an existing cryptographic application for automation purposes. | Java, Netbeans
- (EODAS) Created a user interface to create countermeasure and obscuration files which allow users to choose and edit their own data points. | C++, Visual Studio
- (EODAS) Operated EODAS Bench equipment to verify that CMMod Tool output files were correctly read and processed by the EODAS Operational Flight Program

Walmart Labs

Software Developer | Reston, VA | Jun 2017- Aug 2017

Interned at Walmart Labs in order to develop a tool to return the sales velocity for specified items across all US based Walmart stores in real-time.

- Load tested the API using Gatling to ensure that it will work under expected circumstances.
- Showed the final tool to high-ranking managers in the Walmart community.

Naval Surface Warfare Center, Dahlgren Division

Software Engineer | Dahlgren, VA | May 2016- March 2017

Interned at the Naval Surface Warfare Center working for the Tomahawk program.

• Developed a portion of a weapon's simulation that retrieved vital information about the weapon from a centralized server using C++ and Qt Creator.